Harlan Fiske Stone Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Supreme Court File: Case File, 1924-1946 (Box 52-73)
  - 1934 Term
    - Penn Central Casualty Co. v. Pennsylvania ex rel. Schnader
    - Pennsylvania v. Williams
    - Perry v. United States
    - Railroad Retirement Board v. Alton RR Co.
    - Schechter Poultry Corp. v. United States (empty)
    - Schnell v. The S.S. Vallescura
    - Senior v. Braden
    - Smith v. Snow
    - Snyder v. Comm'r of Internal Revenue
    - Stewart Dry Goods Co. v. Lewis (empty)
    - United States v. Oregon
    - United States v. West Virginia
    - Waxham v. Smith
    - West v. Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Co.
    - West Ohio Gas Co. v. Public Utilities Comm'n of Ohio
  - 1935 Term (Box 62)
    - Arizona v. California
    - Arizona v. Anelich, Administrator
    - Ashton v. Cameron County District (empty)
    - Ashwander v. Tennessee Valley Authority (empty)
    - Baltimore and Ohio R. Co. v. United States (empty)
    - Beadle v. Spencer
    - Becker v. St. Louis Union Trust Co.
    - Becker Steel Co. v. Cummings
    - Bingham v. Reconstruction Finance Corp.
    - Callaghan v. Reconstruction Finance Corp.
    - Carter v. Carter Coal Co. (empty)
    - Chapman v. Hoage
    - Colgate v. Harvey, Tax Comm'r of Vermont
    - Dismuke v. United States
    - Fisher's Blend Station, Inc. v. Tax Comm'n of Washington
    - Giovanni v. Camden Fire Insurance Association
    - Great Northern Ry. Co. v. Weeks State Tax Comm'r (empty)
    - Helvering v. Helmholz
    - Helvering v. St. Louis Union Trust Co.
    - International Business Machines Corp. v. United States
    - Jones v. Securities and Exchange Commission (empty)
    - Koshland v. Helvering (empty)
    - McFeely v. Commissioner
    - Mallory Lines v. State of Alabama
    - Mayflower Farms, Inc. v. Ten Eyck (empty)
    - Meyer et al v. Kenmore Granville Hotel Co.
    - Milwaukee County v. M.E. White Co.
    - Morehead, Warden v. Tipaldo
    - Morf v. Bingaman
    - Northwestern Bell Telephone Co. v. Nebraska State Railway Commission
    - Oklahoma v. Barnsdall Refineries
    - Raybestos-Manhattan, Inc. v. United States
    - St. Joseph Stock Yards Co. v. United States (empty)
    - Schuylkill Trust Co. v. Pennsylvania
    - Stone v. White
    - Triplett v. Lowell, Dunmore & Dubilier Condenser Corp.
    - United States v. Atkinson
    - United States v. Butler
    - United States v. California
    - United States v. Constantine (empty)
    - United States v. Elgin, Joliet & Eastern Ry. Co.
    - United States v. Kesterton
    - White v. Poor.
    - Whitefield v. Ohio
  - 1936 Term
    - Anniston Mfg. Co. v. Davis (empty)
    - Brush v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue (empty)
    - Carmichael v. Southern Coal & Coke Co.
    - District of Columbia v. Clawans
    - First Bank Stock Corp. v. State of Minnesota
    - Great Northern Ry. v. Washington (empty)
    - Hartford Co. v. Harrison (empty)
    - Herndon v. Lowry
    - Ingles v. Morf
    - Lindsey v. State of Washington (Box 63)
    - New York ex rel. Cohn v. Graves
    - Smith v. Hall Brothers
    - Sonzinsky v. United States
    - Stone v. White
    - Sumi v. Young (empty)
    - Swayne & Hoyt Ltd. v. United States
    - Thomas v. Perkins (empty)
    - United States v. Belmont (empty)
    - United States v. Helvering
    - United States v. Madigan
    - Vermont v. New Hampshire
    - Virginian Ry. Co. v. System Federation No. 40
  - 1937 Term
    - Adam v. Saenger
    - Aetna Insurance Co. v. United Fruit Co.
    - Allen v. Regents of University System of Georgia
    - Arkansas Fuel Oil Co. v. Louisiana ex rel. Muslow (empty)
    - Biddle v. Comm'r of Internal Revenue
    - Bogardus v. Comm'r (empty)
    - Calmar Steamship Corp. v. Taylor
    - Chicago Title Co. v. Wilcox Bldg. Corp. (empty)
    - Christopher v. Brusselback
    - Compania Espanola de Navegacion Maritima, S. A. v. Spanish SS Navemar
    - Connecticut General Life Insurance Co. v. Johnson, Treasurer of California (empty)
    - Guaranty Trust Co. of N.Y. v. Comm'r of Internal Revenue
    - Guaranty Trust Co. of N.Y. v. United States (empty)
    - Helvering v. Bankline Oil Co.
    - Helvering v. Gerhardt
    - Helvering v. Pfeiffer
    - Interstate Circuit, Inc. v. United States
    - Lowe Bros. Co. v. United States
    - McEahern v. Rose, Former Collector
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Pacific Greyhound Lines
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Pennsylvania Greyhound Lines (empty)
    - Natural Gas Pipeline Co. v. Slattery
    - Palmer v. Helvering
    - Petroleum Exploration, Inc. v. Public Service Commission (empty)
    - Smith, Executor v. United States (empty)
    - South Carolina State Highway Dept. v. Barnwell Bros.
    - Texas v. Donoghue (empty)
    - Textile Machine Works v. Louis Hirsch Textile Machines
    - United States v. Carolene Products Co.
    - United States v. Klein, Escheator
    - United States v. O'Donnell
    - Western Livestock v. Bingaman, Comm'r
    - White, Former Collector v. Aronson (empty)
    - Worcester County Trust Co. v. Riley
    - Wright v. United States (empty)
  - 1938 Term
    - Atlas Life Ins. Co. v. Southern, Inc.
    - Bethlehem Steel Co. v. Zurich General Accident & Liability Ins. Co. (empty)
    - Blatt Co. v. United States (empty)
    - Clark v. Gray, Inc.
    - Curry v. McCanless
    - Graves v. Elliott
    - Graves v. O'Keefe
    - Guaranty Trust Co. of New York v. Henwood (Box 64)
    - Gwin, White & Prince, Inc. v. Henneford
    - Hague v. CIO
    - Helvering v. Weaver Co.
    - Interstate Circuit, Inc. v. United States
    - James v. United Artist Corp.
    - MacKay Radio & Tel. Co., Inc. v. Radio Corporation of America
    - Montana v. Bruce
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Columbian Enameling & Stamping Co., Inc.
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Fainblatt
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Fansteel metallurgical Corp. (empty)
    - Pacific Employers Insurance Co. v. Industrial Accident Comm'n of Cal.
    - Schriber-Schroth Co. v. Cleveland Trust Co., Chrysler Corp.
    - Socony-Vacuum Oil Co. v. Smith, Jr.
    - Texas v. Florida
    - Titus v. Wallick
    - United States v. Algoma Lumber Co.
    - United States v. Continental National Bank & Trust Co.
    - United States v. Morgan
    - Welch v. Henry
    - White v. United States
    - Wichita Royalty Co. v. City National Bank of Wichita Falls
    - Wilentz v. Sovereign Camp, Woodmen of the World
  - 1939 Term
    - American Federation of Labor v. National Labor Relations Board
    - Apex Hosiery Co. v. Leader
    - Delaware River Joint Toll Bridge Comm. v. Colburn
    - Dietrick, Receiver v. Greaney
    - Ethyl Gasoline Corp. v. United States
    - Haggar Co. v. Helvering
    - McCarroll v. Dixie Greyhound Lines
    - McGoldrick v. Berwind-White Coal Mining Co. (Box 65)
    - McGoldrick v. Compagnie Generale Trans-Atlantique
    - McGoldrick v. Felt & Tarrant Mfg. Co.
    - McGoldrick v. Gulf Oil Corp.
    - Mauer v. Hamilton, Jr.
    - Minersville School District v. Gobitis
    - Minnesota v. National Tea Company (empty)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers
    - National Licorice Co. v. National Labor Relations Board
    - Pearson v. McGraw
    - Rasquin v. Humphreys
    - Rouw Co. v. Crivella
    - Russell v. Todd
    - Sanford v. Comm'r of Internal Revenue
    - Schneider v. State
    - Securities and Exchange Comm'n v. United States Realty & Improvement Co.
    - Union Stock Yard & Transit Co. v. United States
    - United States v. American Trucking Assn (empty)
    - United States v. Dickerson (empty)
    - United States v. Lowden
    - United States v. Manton
    - United States v. United States Fidelity and Guaranty
  - 1940 Term
    - Beal v. Missouri Pacific Railroad Co.
    - California v. Thompson
    - Continental Oil Co. v. National Labor Relations Board (empty)
    - Electro-Chemical Engraving Co., Inc. v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue
    - Equitable Life Ins. Co. v. Halsey, Stuart & Co.
    - Fashion Originator's Guild v. Federal Trade Commission
    - Frost & Co. v. Coeur D'Alene Mines Corp. (empty)
    - Hansberry v. Lee
    - Harrison v. Schaffner
    - Heinz Co. v. National Labor Relations Board (Box 66)
    - Helvering v. Eubank
    - Helvering v. Hammel
    - Helvering v. Horst
    - Helvering v. Hutchings
    - Hines v. Davidowitz
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Express Publishing Co.
    - New York v. Feiring
    - Nye v. United States
    - Oklahoma ex, rek, Phillips v. Atkinson
    - Opp Cotton Mills, Inc. v. Wage & Hour Division of Labor Department
    - Palmer v. Connecticut Ry. & Lighting Co.
    - Phelps Dodge Corp. v. National Labor Relations Board
    - Pittsburgh Plate Glass Co. v. National Labor Relations Board
    - Royal Indemnity Co. v. United States
    - Ryerson v. United States
    - Schriber-Schroth Co. v. Clevland Trust Co.
    - Shamrock Oil & Gas Corp. v. Sheets
    - Singer & Sons v. Union Pacific Railroad Co.
    - Stern v. Gillman
    - Superior Bath House Co. v. McCarroll
    - United States v. Classic
    - United States v. Darby
    - United States v. Falcone
    - United States v. Hutcheson
    - United States v. Pelzer
    - United States v. Sherwood
    - West v. American Telephone & Telegraph Co.
    - West India Oil Co. v. Domenech
    - Wright v. Union Central Life Ins. Co.
  - 1941 Term (Box 67)
    - Alabama v. King & Boozer
    - Baltimore & Ohio R. Co. v. Kepner (empty)
    - B. & B. Chemical Co. v. Ellis
    - Bridges v. California (empty)
    - Brillhart v. Excess Ins. Co.
    - Cloverleaf Butter Co. v. Patterson
    - Ex parte Don Ascanio Colonna
    - Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. v. United States
    - Commerical Molasses Corp. v. New York Tank Barge Corp., (2 folders)
    - Cudahy Packing Co. v. Holland
    - Cuno Engineering Corp. v. Automatic Devices Corp.
    - Curry, Commissioner v. United States
    - Duckworth v. Arkansas
    - Exhibit Supply Co. v. Ace Patents Co.
    - Federal Power Commission v. Natural Gas Pipeline Co.
    - Glasser v. United States (empty)
    - Goldman v. United States
    - Goldstein v. United States
    - Gorman v. Washington University
    - Graves v. Schmidlapp
    - Gray v. Powell
    - Helvering v. Safe Deposit & Trust Co.
    - Hill v. Texas
    - Illinois Natural Gas Co. v. Central Illinois Public Service Co.
    - Jacob v. New York City (empty)
    - Jones v. City of Opelika
    - MacGregor, Executor v. State Mutual Life Assurance Co.
    - Memphis Natural Gas Co. v. Beeler
    - Miles v. Illinois Central R. Co. (empty)
    - Morton Salt Co. v. G.S. Suppiger Co.
    - National Broadcasting Co., Inc. v. United States
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Automotive Maintenance Machinery Co.
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Nevada Consolidated Copper Co.
    - New York, Chicago, & St. Louis RR. Co. v. Frank
    - Northern Pacific Ry. Co. et al. v. United States (empty)
    - Overnight Motor Transportation Co. v. Missel (empty)
    - Pearce v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue (empty)
    - Pecheur Lozenge Co. v. National Candy Co.
    - Peyton v. Railway Express Agency, Inc.
    - Pink v. A.A.A. Highway Express, Inc.
    - Prudence Realization Corp. v. Geist
    - Puerto Rico v. Hermanos et al. (empty)
    - Riley v. New York Trust Co.
    - Skinner v. Oklahoma (empty)
    - Southern Ry. Co. v. Painter (empty) (Box 68)
    - Southport Petroleum Co. v. National Labor Relations Board (empty)
    - Swift & Co. v. United States
    - Toucey v. New York Life Ins. Co. (empty)
    - United States v. Kales
    - United States v. Local 807
    - United States v. Malphurs (empty)
    - United States v. Pink
    - United States ex rel. Coy v. United States
    - United States v. Univis Lens Co., Inc.
    - United States v. Wrightwood Dairy Co.
    - Waley v. Johnson
  - 1942 Term
    - Aguilar v. Standard Oil Co. of New Jersey
    - Bailey v. Central Vermont Ry. Co. (empty)
    - Barringer & Co. v. United States
    - Bartchy v. United States
    - Bowles v. United States
    - In re William Bradley
    - Braverman v. United States
    - Burford v. Sun Oil (empty)
    - Busey v. District of Columbia
    - Cole v. Violette
    - Davis v. Dept. of Labor
    - Ex parte Elmer Davis
    - Dept. of Banking of Nebraska v. Pink
    - Detroit Bank v. United States
    - Douglas v. City of Jeanette
    - Dunn v. Ohio
    - Federal Security Adm'n v. Quaker Oats Co.
    - Great Lakes Dredge & Dock Co. v. Huffman
    - Hastings v. Selby Oil & Gas Co. (empty)
    - Helvering v. Stuart
    - Hendry Co. v. Moore
    - Hirabayashi v. United States
    - Holley v. Lawrence (empty)
    - Hoopeston Canning Co. v. Cullen
    - Huges v. Wendell (empty)
    - Illinois Commerce Commission v. Thompson
    - Interstate Transit Lines v. Commissioner (empty)
    - Jersey City Central Power & Light Co. v. Federal Power Commission
    - Jones v. City of Opelika
    - Kelley v. Everglades Drainage District
    - Lockerty v. Phillips
    - Mandeville v. Canterbury
    - Mangus v. Miller
    - Marconi Wireless Telegraph Co. v. United States
    - Marshall Field & Co. v. National Labor Relations Board
    - Martin v. Struthers
    - Matton Steamboat Co., Inc. v. Murphy (Box 69)
    - Michigan v. United States
    - Natural Milk Producers Ass'n v. San Francisco
    - New York ex rel. Whitman v. Wilson
    - O'Donnell v. Great Lakes Dredge & Dock Co.
    - Oklahoma Tax Commission v. United States
    - Osment v. Pitcairn
    - Owens v. Union Pacific RR. Co. (empty)
    - Parker v. Brown
    - Penn Dairies, Inc. v. Milk Control Commission of Pennsylvania
    - Ex parte Quirin
    - Ex parte Republican of Peru
    - Roche v. Evaporated Milk Co.
    - Saint Pierre v. United States
    - Schneiderman v. United States
    - Sharpe v. Buchanan
    - Sola Electric Co. v. Jefferson Electric Co.
    - Steffler v. United States
    - Stephan v. United States
    - Tileston v. Ullman
    - United States v. Johnson
    - United States v. Swift & Co.
    - Viereck v. United States
    - Virginia Electric Power Co. v. National Labor Relations Board
    - Virginia Hotel Corp. v. Helvering
    - Wells v. United States
    - Wragge v. Federal Land Bank of New Orleans
    - Yasui v. United States
  - 1943 Term
    - Ex parte Abernathy (empty)
    - Anderson National Bank v. Luckett
    - Columbia Gas & Electric Corp. v. American Fuel & Power Co.
    - DeCastro v. Board of Commissioners of San Juan
    - Dobson v. Commissioner
    - Douglas v. Commissioner
    - Eastern Central Motor Carriers Association v. United States (empty)
    - Flournoy v. Wiener (Box 70)
    - Ex parte Henry Hawk
    - Hazel-Atlas Glass Co. v. Hartford-Empire Co.
    - Hill v. Hawes
    - Huddleston et al. v. Dwyer
    - Hunter Co., Inc. v. McHugh
    - Illinois Steel Co. v. Baltimore & Ohio RR. Co.
    - International Harvester Corp. v. Wisconsin Dept. of Taxation
    - Interstate Commerce Commission et al. v. Hoboken Manufacturers' RR. Co.
    - Magnolia Petroleum Co. v. Hunt
    - Mahnich v. Southern Steamship Co.
    - Medo Photo Supply Corp. v. National Labor Relations Board
    - Mario Mercado e Hijos v. Commins
    - Meredith v. City of Winter Haven
    - Mortensen v. United States
    - Northwest Airlines, Inc. v. State of Minnesota
    - Pollock v. Williams, Sheriff (empty)
    - Roberts v. United States
    - Estate of Rogers v. Commissioner
    - Sartor v. Arkansas Natural Gas Corp.
    - Shawkee Mfg. Co. v. Hartford Co. (empty)
    - Snowden v. Hughes
    - Tennant, Adm'x v. Peoria & Pekin Union Ry. (empty)
    - Tennessee Coal, Iron & RR. Co. v. Muscoda Local
    - United States v. Ballard
    - United States v. Marshall Transport Co.
    - United States v. Myers
    - United States v. South-Eastern Underwriters Association
    - United States v. Wabash RR. Co.
    - United States ex rel. McCann v. Adams, Warden
    - Walling v. James V. Reuter, Inc.
    - Yakus v. United States
  - 1944 Term (Box 71)
    - Akins v. Texas
    - Alabama v. United States
    - Alabama State Federation of Labor v. McAdory
    - Associated Press v. United States
    - Barber v. Barber
    - Barrett Line, Inc. v. United States (empty)
    - Bates v. United States
    - Blair v. Baltimore & Ohio RR Co. (empty)
    - Borden Co. v. Borella (empty)
    - Bridges v. Wixon
    - Brooklyn Savings Bank v. O'Neil
    - Busby and Lowrey v. Electric Utilities Employees Union
    - Charleston Federal Savings & Loan Ass'n v. Anderson
    - Coffman v. Breeze Corporations, Inc. and the United States
    - Coffman v. Federal Laboratories, Inc. and the United States
    - Colorado Interstate Gas Co. v. Canadian River Gas Co.
    - Colorado Wyoming Gas Co. v. Federal Power Commission (empty)
    - Commissioner of Internal Revenue v. Smith
    - C.I. O. v. McAdory (empty)
    - Corn Products Refining Co. v. Federal Trade Commission
    - Cramer v. United States
    - Elgin, Joliet,, & Eastern R. Co. v. Burley
    - Federal Trade Commission v. Staley Mfg. Co.
    - Freeman v. Hewit
    - Gemsco, Inc. v. Walling (empty)
    - Georgia v. Pennsylvania Railroad
    - Hartford Empire v. United States
    - Hill v. Florida ex rel. Watson
    - Hooven & Allison Co. v. Evatt
    - House v. Mayo, State Prison Custodian
    - Hunt v. Crumboch
    - Industrial Addition Association v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue
    - Jewell Ridge Corp. v. Local 6167
    - Keegan v. United States
    - Korematsu v. United States
    - Lutz v. Ragen See Container 72, White v. Ragen
    - McCullough v. Kammerer Corp. and Baash-Ross Tool Co. (Box 72)
    - McDonald v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue
    - McKenzie v. Irving Trust Co.
    - Mackey v. Kaiser
    - Malinski v. People of New York
    - Merrill v. Fahs, Collector of Internal Revenue
    - North Carolina v. United States (empty)
    - Otis & Co. v. Securities and Exchange Commission
    - Panhandle Eastern Pipeline Co. v. Federal Power Commission
    - Phillips, Inc. v. Walling (empty)
    - Pope v. United States
    - Prudence Realization Corp. v. Ferris
    - Regal Knitwear Co. v. National Labor Relations Board (empty)
    - Republic of Mexico v. Hoffman
    - Screws v. United States
    - Southern Pacific Co. v. Arizona ex rel. Sullivan, Atty General
    - Special Equipment Co. v. Coe, Comm'r
    - Steele v. Louisville & Nashville RR. Co. and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen
    - 10 East 40th St. Bldg., Inc. v. Callus (empty)
    - Thomas v. Collins, Sheriff (empty)
    - Tiller v. Atlantic Coastline RR. (empty)
    - Trust U/W of Bingham v. Commissioner
    - Tunstall v. Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen (empty)
    - United States v. Carmen Beach
    - United States v. Johnson
    - United States v. Townsley (empty)
    - United States v. Willow River Power Co. (empty)
    - United States Alkali Export Ass'n et al. v. United States
    - Walling v. Youngerman-Reynolds Hardwood Co. Same v. Harnischfeger Corp.
    - White v. Ragen Lutz v. Ragen
    - Williams v. North Carolina
    - Young v. Higbee Co. (empty)
  - 1945 Term
    - American Federation of Labor et al. v. Watson et al. (empty)
    - Asbury Hospital v. Cass Country, undated
    - Bailey v. Anderson, State Highway Commissioner of Virginia
    - Bell v. Hood (empty)
    - Bigelow v. RKO Radio Pictures, Inc.
    - Chickasaw Nation v. United States
    - Commissioner v. Tower (empty)
    - Duncan v. Kahanamoku, Sheriff
    - Estep v. United States
    - Fernadez, Collector v. Wiener
    - Girouard v. United States
    - Griffin v. Griffin
    - Heiser v. Woodruff
    - Hercules Gasoline Co. v. Commissioner (empty)
    - International Shoe Co. v. State of Washington
    - Lavender v. Kurn Trustees (empty)
    - Lusthaus v. Commissioner
    - Markham, Alien Property Custodian v. Allen
    - Marsh v. Alabama
    - May Stores Co. v. Labor Board (Box 73)
    - Mississippi Publishing Corp. v. Murphree
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Cheney California Lumber Co. (empty)
    - New York and Saratoga Springs v. United States
    - Schenley Distillers Corp. et al. v. United States
    - Scott Paper Co. v. Marcalus Mfg. Co. and Nicholas Marcalus
    - Seas Shipping Co., Inc. v. Sieracki
    - S.R.A. Inc. v. State of Minnesota
    - Swanson v. Marra Brothers, Inc.
    - Tucker v. Texas (empty)
    - United States v. Carbone
    - United States v. New York Telephone Co.
    - United States v. Rice
    - United States v. Rompel
    - Wilson v. Cook
    - In the matter of Yamashita
    - Unidentified cases
- Supreme Court File: Correspondence, 1925-1946 (Box 73-79)
  Letters received, copies of letters sent, memoranda, and other material, divided into two groups-correspondence with other Justices, arranged alphabetically by correspondent, and correspondence with attorneys and petitioners. Arranged chronologically.
  - Correspondence with other justices (Box 73)
    - Black, Hugo Lafayette
      - 1937-1938
      - 1939-1941
      - 1942-1944
      - 1945-1946, undated
      - Miscellany
    - Brandeis, Louis D.
      - 1925-1932
      - 1933-1937
      - 1938-1941, undated
      - Miscellany
    - Burton, Harold H., 1945
    - Butler, Pierce, 1925-1939
    - Byrnes, James F. (Box 74)
      - Miscellany
    - Cardozo, Benjamin N. See also Container 8, Cardozo
      - 1932-1935
      - 1936-1938, undated
      - Miscellany
    - Douglas, William O.
      - 1938-1939
      - 1940-1941
      - 1942
      - 1943
      - 1944
      - 1945-1946, undated
      - Miscellany
    - Frankfurter, Felix See also Container 13, Frankfurter
      - 1939, (2 folders)
      - 1941
      - 1942
      - 1943, (2 folders)
      - 1944, (2 folders)
      - 1945 (Box 75)
      - 1946
      - Undated, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany
    - Holmes, Oliver Wendell
      - 1925-1927
      - 1928-1929
      - 1930-1931, 1935, undated
    - Hughes, Charles Evans See also Container 17, Hughes
      - 1930-1931
      - 1932-1933
      - 1934-1935
      - 1936-1937
      - 1938-1939
      - 1940-1941, undated
    - Jackson, Robert Houghout See also Container 17, Jackson
      - 1941-1942
      - 1943-1944
      - 1945-1946
      - Miscellany
    - McReynolds, James C., 1925-1940, undated (Box 76)
    - Murphy, Frank
      - 1939-1941
      - 1942-1944
      - 1945-1946, undated
      - Miscellany
    - Reed, Stanley F.
      - 1938-1939
      - 1940-1942
      - 1943-1944
      - 1945-1946
      - Miscellany
    - Roberts, Owen J.
      - 1930-1931
      - 1932-1934
      - 1935-1938
      - 1939-1940
      - 1941-1942
      - 1943
      - 1944
      - 1945, undated
    - Rutledge, Wiley B.
      - 1941, 1943
      - 1944
      - 1945
      - 1946
    - Sanford, Edward T., 1925-1929, undated
    - Sutherland, George See also Container 28, Sutherland
      - 1925-1938, undated
    - Taft, William Howard
      - 1925
      - 1926-1927
      - 1928 (Box 77)
      - 1929-1930, undated
      - Miscellany
    - Van Devanter, Willis See also Container 29, Van Devanter
      - 1926-1936, undated
    - Memoranda to the court
      - 1941
      - 1942
      - 1943
      - 1944
      - 1945
      - 1946
  - Correspondence with attorneys and petitioners
    - 1928-1929
    - 1929
    - 1930, (3 folders)
    - 1931 (Box 78)
    - 1932, (2 folders)
    - 1933, (4 folders)
    - 1934
    - 1935 (Box 79)
    - 1936
    - 1937, (2 folders)
    - 1938, (2 folders)
    - 1939, (2 folders)
    - 1940, (2 folders)
    - 1941
    - 1942, (2 folders)
    - 1943
    - 1944
- Supreme Court File: General Office File, 1925-1944 (Box 80-82)
  Correspondence, memoranda, notes, and near-print and printed material relating to administrative and other details of Stone's work as a Supreme Court Justice.
  Arranged alphabetically by subject and type of material.
  - Administrative Office of the U.S. Courts (Box 80)
    - 1939, May-Oct.
    - 1939-1944, Nov.
  - Appointed counsel, 1943-1944